<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>testimonial3 &#8211; Percept Systems</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials_category/testimonial3/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com</link>
	<description>Software Development Company</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 11:37:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.14</generator>
	<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/4497/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 07:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://ps.blockchainpeer.com/?post_type=dt_testimonials&#038;p=4497</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Kulwant has many years of full stack, and engineering leadership experience. He is also excellent at deciphering needs from technical and business managers. More-over, his dedication to delivery is one of his most outstanding qualities even beyond his almost countless languages and approaches he practices in his work. Every single project over the years I&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/4497/"></a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em></p>
<div style="color:white; font-family:montserrat;">Kulwant has many years of full stack, and engineering leadership experience. He is also excellent at deciphering needs from technical and business managers. More-over, his dedication to delivery is one of his most outstanding qualities even beyond his almost countless languages and approaches he practices in his work. Every single project over the years I have involved Kulwant in, he has delivered, even under very tight deadlines, high pressure, and uncertainty. Kulwant is an asset to any team, and has skills from the bottom of the stack all the way to the top and including process and management. If you work with Kulwant, you will see value immediately up on adding him to your team.</div>
<p></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/4497/"></a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/4495/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 07:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://ps.blockchainpeer.com/?post_type=dt_testimonials&#038;p=4495</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Kulwant is beyond a full stack automation engineer who also develops QA automation solutions. Kulwant also manages his own technical team, assists us in 24hr dev/qa continuous development integration during US and Indian time zones. His knowledge in browser based automation with selenium, and his contribution to building us desktop testing tools needed to run&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/4495/"></a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em></p>
<div style="color:white; font-family:montserrat;">Kulwant is beyond a full stack automation engineer who also develops QA automation solutions. Kulwant also manages his own technical team, assists us in 24hr dev/qa continuous development integration during US and Indian time zones. His knowledge in browser based automation with selenium, and his contribution to building us desktop testing tools needed to run thousands of parallel tests to support our regular releases was critical to the evolution of our QA departments service charter and to our continuing platform growth and health. Ive worked with Kulwant for more years than I can remember, and we will definitely hire him again. With so many challenging projects under our belts over the years, I am always able to rely on Kulwant to deliver. 10 stars Kulwant!</div>
<p></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/4495/"></a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/1392/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://ctu.blockchainteam.in/?post_type=dt_testimonials&#038;p=1392</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>CHAD COLLINS, CEO Working with Percept since last 5 years, where I connected with Kulwant via Upwork. Kulwant is an excellent developer. He was open and communicative. he was also very knowledgeable and reliable. We would definitely continue our work with Percept in future..</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/1392/"></a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="padding-top: 1em;"><span style="color: #ffffff;"><em><span style="font-family: Arvo; font-size: 15px;"><strong>CHAD COLLINS, CEO</strong><br />
Working with Percept since last 5 years, where I connected with Kulwant via Upwork. Kulwant is an excellent developer. He was open and communicative. he was also very knowledgeable and reliable. We would definitely continue our work with Percept in future..</span></em></span></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/dt_testimonials/1392/"></a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
