<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BLOG &#8211; Percept Systems</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com</link>
	<description>Software Development Company</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:29:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.14</generator>
	<item>
		<title>HOW TO CHOOSE THE IDEAL DIGITAL MARKETING SERVICES FOR YOUR BUSINESS?</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/how-to-choose-the-right-digital-marketing-services/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital marketing services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digitl marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEO]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5359</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>As increasingly more business is performed online, and more and more potential customers look for products on the web, you need a strong digital marketing presence and plan set up, particularly if you are starting a new business. The importance of having a digital marketing agency for a business is obvious. It is in the nature&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/how-to-choose-the-right-digital-marketing-services/">HOW TO CHOOSE THE IDEAL DIGITAL MARKETING SERVICES FOR YOUR BUSINESS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As increasingly more business is performed online, and more and more potential customers look for products on the web, you need a strong digital marketing presence and plan set up, particularly if you are starting a new business. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">The importance of having a digital marketing agency for a business is obvious. It is in the nature of any firm/company to focus on the primary objectives that define the company. This entails appointing other relevant works like digital marketing to external agencies. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A lot of that relies upon who your company is and what you do. So the initial step will be to acknowledge marketing issue and the need of a digital marketing agency. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">For instance, a company that develops software will commit the majority of its workforce to developing and selling software alone. The business of that company is software, not marketing or advertising; and regardless of whether it does its very own marketing campaigns, there&#8217;s a superior chance that a marketing agency, whose only business is creating marketing campaigns, will carry out the responsibility much b</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">etter than the software company&#8217;s marketing part. </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">So how can one determine the right digital marketing agency to work with? </span></h2>
<h3></h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3><em><strong>Research: </strong></em></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Quite obviously, there are a great deal of trustworthy digital marketing agencies out there to choose from. However, there are some who will promise the world and string you along while they collect more and more money and never deliver any real results. Since this is obviously a situation you want to avoid, it’s vital that you do your homework to separate the worthy from those who only pretend. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">The most ideal approach to employ an agency that will deliver results, is to find one that has a good track record with regards to this.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3><em><strong>Long term plan </strong></em></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since your association with a digital marketing agency is a partnership, you&#8217;ll need a company that can help drive your company forward. This will be a vital partnership that will build your business toward a better future, and one that you should see as a long term relationship. Picking the correct company will take some time, but it will be worth it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3><em><strong>Look for the worth, not price </strong></em></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cost will clearly be a consideration when it comes to taking the decision, but you shouldn&#8217;t go with whoever has the lesser rate. The less expensive agency will hardly offer you the best services. Ask away for the value for your money, and get an understanding of what would be expected from you as well as the company. This can ensure that your money isn&#8217;t wasted, rather invested into your company&#8217;s future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><em>Percept Software Systems Private Limited provides top-notch digital marketing services. We specialize in ROI-aimed lead generation and digital marketing &#8211; in its various ways to maximize your brand’s online and offline presence with eye-catching visuals to amazing content. We take a modified approach to build you a plan based on your niche and current position within that competitive environment. You can learn more about our <a href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/digital-marketing/">digital marketing services</a> or get in touch to have a free assessment today.</em></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/how-to-choose-the-right-digital-marketing-services/">HOW TO CHOOSE THE IDEAL DIGITAL MARKETING SERVICES FOR YOUR BUSINESS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>CUSTOMIZED ECOMMERCE WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT SERVICES</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/customized-ecommerce-website-development-services/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5014</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Online business is booming and with the ecommerce boom, comes the need for ecommerce website development. Ecommerce websites have to be really clutter breaking and therefore, the need for a path breaking ecommerce website development services. We, at Webmobinfo, provide you with customized ecommerce website development services that is aligned to your business objective and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/customized-ecommerce-website-development-services/">CUSTOMIZED ECOMMERCE WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT SERVICES</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Online business is booming and with the ecommerce boom, comes the need for ecommerce website development. Ecommerce websites have to be really clutter breaking and therefore, the need for a path breaking ecommerce website development services. We, at Webmobinfo, provide you with customized ecommerce website development services that is aligned to your business objective and provides unique solutions suited to your needs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/customized-ecommerce-website-development-services/">CUSTOMIZED ECOMMERCE WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT SERVICES</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>BLOCKCHAIN TECHNOLOGY</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/blockchain-technology-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 11:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5012</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain is an emerging way for businesses, industries, and public organisations to almost instantaneously make and verify transactions—streamlining business processes, saving money, and reducing the potential for fraud. At its core, a blockchain is a data structure that is used to create a digital transaction ledger that, instead of resting with a single provider, is&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/blockchain-technology-2/">BLOCKCHAIN TECHNOLOGY</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain is an emerging way for businesses, industries, and public organisations to almost instantaneously make and verify transactions—streamlining business processes, saving money, and reducing the potential for fraud. At its core, a blockchain is a data structure that is used to create a digital transaction ledger that, instead of resting with a single provider, is shared among a distributed network of computers.<br />
The result is a more open, transparent, and publically verifiable system that will fundamentally change the way we think about exchanging value and assets, enforcing contracts, and sharing data across industries. The applications using blockchain are almost limitless, ranging from loans, bonds, and payments to more efficient supply chains to even identity management and verification.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/blockchain-technology-2/">BLOCKCHAIN TECHNOLOGY</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>WHAT IS ERC-20 AND WHAT DOES IT MEAN FOR ETHEREUM?</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-erc-20-and-what-does-it-mean-for-ethereum/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 10:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5009</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum the popular cryptocurrency and blockchain system, is based on the use of tokens which can be bought, sold, or traded. There are several different tokens which may be used in conjunction with Ethereum, and these differ from ether, which is the currency native to the Ethereum blockchain. Tokens, in this case, represent digital assets&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-erc-20-and-what-does-it-mean-for-ethereum/">WHAT IS ERC-20 AND WHAT DOES IT MEAN FOR ETHEREUM?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum the popular cryptocurrency and blockchain system, is based on the use of tokens which can be bought, sold, or traded. There are several different tokens which may be used in conjunction with Ethereum, and  these differ from ether, which is the currency native to the Ethereum blockchain. Tokens, in this case, represent digital assets that can have a variety of values attached. They can represent assets as diverse as vouchers, IOUs, or even objects in the real world. In this way, tokens are essentially smart contracts that make use of the Ethereum blockchain. One of the most significant token standards of all for Ethereum is called ERC-20, which was developed about a year and a half ago.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-erc-20-and-what-does-it-mean-for-ethereum/">WHAT IS ERC-20 AND WHAT DOES IT MEAN FOR ETHEREUM?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN BLOCKCHAIN AND DATABASE</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-the-difference-between-blockchain-and-database-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5006</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain is defined as “a system that’s secure without a higher authority, distributed across many strangers’ computers, yet tamper-proof, and promises a mechanism for trust mediated directly between individuals”. Essentially, by providing a distributed means to guarantee and verify transactions, the blockchain offers the ultimate opportunity to cut out the middleman. If trust and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-the-difference-between-blockchain-and-database-2/">WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN BLOCKCHAIN AND DATABASE</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain is defined as “a system that’s secure without a higher authority, distributed across many strangers’ computers, yet tamper-proof, and promises a mechanism for trust mediated directly between individuals”. Essentially, by providing a distributed means to guarantee and verify transactions, the blockchain offers the ultimate opportunity to cut out the middleman. If trust and robustness aren’t an issue, there’s nothing a blockchain can do that a regular database cannot</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-the-difference-between-blockchain-and-database-2/">WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN BLOCKCHAIN AND DATABASE</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>WHAT IS A SMART CONTRACTS?</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-a-smart-contracts/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 10:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5003</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>In the easiest form, it is an agreement between couple of multiple parties online that can be automatically executed on a transparent blockchain using cryptocurrency. In the context of blockchains and cryptocurrencies, smart contracts are: – pre-written logic (computer code), – stored and replicated on a distributed storage platform (eg a blockchain), – executed/run by&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-a-smart-contracts/">WHAT IS A SMART CONTRACTS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the easiest form, it is an agreement between couple of multiple parties online that can be automatically executed on a transparent blockchain using cryptocurrency.<br />
In the context of blockchains and cryptocurrencies, smart contracts are:<br />
– pre-written logic (computer code),<br />
– stored and replicated on a distributed storage platform (eg a blockchain),<br />
– executed/run by a network of computers (usually the same ones running the blockchain),<br />
– and can result in ledger updates (cryptocurrency payments, etc).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-a-smart-contracts/">WHAT IS A SMART CONTRACTS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>IOTA – THE BLOCKCHAIN KILLER</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/iota-the-blockchain-killer/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 10:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=5000</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>IOTA is a revolutionary new transactional settlement and data integrity layer for the Internet of Things. It’s based on new distributed ledger architecture, the Tangle, which overcomes the inefficiencies of current Blockchain designs and introduces a new way of reaching consensus in a decentralized peer-to-peer system. For the first time ever, through IOTA people can&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/iota-the-blockchain-killer/">IOTA – THE BLOCKCHAIN KILLER</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IOTA is a revolutionary new transactional settlement and data integrity layer for the Internet of Things. It’s based on new distributed ledger architecture, the Tangle, which overcomes the inefficiencies of current Blockchain designs and introduces a new way of reaching consensus in a decentralized peer-to-peer system. For the first time ever, through IOTA people can transfer money without any fees. This means that even infinitesimally small nanopayments can be made through IOTA.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/iota-the-blockchain-killer/">IOTA – THE BLOCKCHAIN KILLER</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>WHAT IS HYPERLEDGER?</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-hyperledger/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=4997</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Hyperledger (or the Hyperledger project) is an umbrella project of open source blockchains and related tools started in December 2015 by the Linux Foundation, to support the collaborative development of blockchain-based distributed ledgers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-hyperledger/">WHAT IS HYPERLEDGER?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hyperledger (or the Hyperledger project) is an umbrella project of open source blockchains and related tools<br />
started in December 2015 by the Linux Foundation, to support the collaborative development of blockchain-based<br />
distributed ledgers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/what-is-hyperledger/">WHAT IS HYPERLEDGER?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>PUBLIC VS PRIVATE BLOCKCHAINS</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/public-vs-private-blockchains/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 08:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=4994</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>There is a big diﬀerence in what technologies you need, depending on whether you allow anyone to write to your blockchain, or known, vetted participants. Bitcoin allows anyone to write to its ledger.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/public-vs-private-blockchains/">PUBLIC VS PRIVATE BLOCKCHAINS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is a big diﬀerence in what technologies you need, depending on whether you allow anyone to write to your blockchain, or known, vetted participants. Bitcoin allows anyone to write to its ledger.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/public-vs-private-blockchains/">PUBLIC VS PRIVATE BLOCKCHAINS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS- IS IT AN ETHEREUM KILLER?</title>
		<link>https://www.perceptsystems.com/eos-is-it-an-ethereum-killer/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 07:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.perceptsystems.com/?p=4991</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>• EOS is a blockchain-based, decentralized operating system, designed to support commercial-scale decentralized applications by providing all of the necessary core functionality, enabling businesses to build blockchain applications in a way similar to web-based applications. • EOS’s asynchronous communication and parallel processing provide scalability, while its ownership model eliminates transaction fees. These features make EOS&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/eos-is-it-an-ethereum-killer/">EOS- IS IT AN ETHEREUM KILLER?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>• EOS is a blockchain-based, decentralized operating system, designed to support commercial-scale decentralized applications by providing all of the necessary core functionality, enabling businesses to build blockchain applications in a way similar to web-based applications.<br />
• EOS’s asynchronous communication and parallel processing provide scalability, while its ownership model eliminates transaction fees. These features make EOS a serious competitor of Ethereum (although EOS’s ICO actually supports Ethereum).<br />
• EOS uses delegated-proof-of-stake and introduces the ability to fix bugs and rollback changes with supermajority consensus.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com/eos-is-it-an-ethereum-killer/">EOS- IS IT AN ETHEREUM KILLER?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.perceptsystems.com">Percept Systems</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
